A Guide to the McLean Citizens Association Records, 1922-2014 [bulk]
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 4: Subject Files, 1947-2003
  - Dulles Access Road Extension, 1978-1981 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Fairfax Water and Sewer Survey, 1947-1949 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Flood Control, 1972, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Franklin Sherman Playground, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Hazleton Laboratories, 1974-1986 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Hazleton Laboratories, 1987-1989 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Hazleton Laboratories, 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Haycock Longfellow Park, 1994-1997 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Haycock Longfellow Park, 1998-2002, Undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Incorporation/Annexation of McLean, 1957-1961, Undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Land Ownership Records, 1922-1970 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Langley Methodist Church Property, 1952-1953 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Leighton Cain--Obituary, 2000 July 5 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - "McLean…A Vision for the Future Now!" Transportation Report, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - McLean Little League--Application, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - McLean Little League--BZA Appeals, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - McLean Little League--BZA Presentation, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - McLean Little League--Chesapeake Bay Preservation Act, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - McLean Little League--Clippings, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - McLean Little League--Correspondence, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - McLean Little League--Correspondence Against, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - McLean Little League--Correspondence For, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - McLean Little League--Foxhall Road News, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - McLean Little League--SE 98-D-047/SP 98-D-027 [floppy disk], 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - McLean Little League--SP 90-D-012 Permit, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - McLean Little League--Staff Report, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - McLean Little League--Technical Report, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - McLean Master Plan, 1963-1967 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - McLean Recreation Council Organization and Procedure, Undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Merrimac Property, 1978-1982 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1974-1979, Undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Neighborhood Association Survey, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Pimmit Run Greenway, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - PRC-Hazel Peterson Site, 1974-1990 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - PRC-Hazel Peterson Site, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - PRC-Hazel Peterson Site, 1994 May (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - PRC-Hazel Peterson Site, 1994 June-July (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - PRC-Hazel Peterson Site, Undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Route 123 Property Sale, 1954-1959, Undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Senate Bill No. 270, 1989-1992, Undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Subdivision of Lots on Private Streets, 1992-1993 April (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Subdivision of Lots on Private Streets, 1993 May-September, Undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Subdivision of Lots on Private Streets--Public Street Waiver Request for Skallerup Property [photo], 1993-1994 March (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Subdivision of Lots on Private Streets--Public Street Waiver Request for Skallerup Property, April-September 1994, Undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Trees, 1992-1995 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Tyson-McLean Associates, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Series 5: Related Organizations, 1964-2003
  - Sub-series 5-1: Coalition to Save Evans Farm, 1966-2003
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Rezoning Application (RZ 1998-DR-049), 1998 September-1999 April (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Rezoning Application (RZ 1998-DR-049), 1999 May-1999 July (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Out-of-Turn Plan Amendment, 1997-1999 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--County Documents, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Correspondence, 1998 July-August (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Correspondence, 1998 September-October (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Correspondence, 1998 November-1999 January (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Correspondence, 1999 February-1999 March (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Correspondence, 1999 April (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Correspondence, 1999 May-2000, Undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Press Releases, 1998-1999, Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--West*Group Negotiations, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Appraisal, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Organization, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Financial Documents, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Meeting Sign-in Sheets, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Fundraising, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--McLean Citizens Foundation--"Save Evans Farm Fund" [floppy disk], 1998 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Fall Family Festival, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--March Music Fest, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Demonstration, 1999 May (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Handouts, 1998-1999, Undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Volunteer Lists, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Contacts, Undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Web Site, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Canvasser's Guide, 1998, n.d (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Petitions (1/3), 1998 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Petitions (2/3), 1998 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Petitions (3/3), 1998 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Resolutions, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--WETA Pledge Drive, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Research--Land Use, 1966-2000, Undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Research--Contributions to Supervisors, 1970-1999, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--"Evans Farm Inn-McLean, Virginia: A Strive [sic] for Consensus Planning", 2000 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Clippings, 1997-1998 August (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Clippings, 1998 September-1998 December (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Clippings, 1999-2001 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Clippings, Undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--"Save Evans Farm" Stickers, Undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Photographs [photos], Undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--Evans Farm Notecards, Undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--"Evans Farm" VHS Tapes, 1998 November 7 and 1999 June 8 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Coalition to Save Evans Farm--McLean Land Conservancy, Inc., 2000-2003 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Sub-series 5-2: McLean Citizens Foundation, 2001-2003
    - McLean Citizens Foundation--Haycock Elementary Trees [photo], 2001-2003, Undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Sub-series 5-3: McLean Community Center, 1964-1982
    - McLean Community Center--By Laws, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - McLean Community Center--Elections, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - McLean Community Center--Advisory Council, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - McLean Community Center--Governing Board Meeting Attendance, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - McLean Community Center--Budgets, 1969-1982, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - McLean Community Center--Public Hearing Packet, 1971 January 28 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - McLean Community Center--Grand Opening and Dedication, 1975 October 19 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - McLean Community Center--Correspondence and Notes, 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - McLean Community Center--Correspondence and Notes, 1971-1983, Undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - McLean Community Center--Memoranda of Understanding with Fairfax County, 1971-1981 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - McLean Community Center--Proposed Lease of Franklin Sherman School, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - McLean Community Center--Meeting Room Reservations, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 4)